SEDRAK ADOYAN

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Tbilisi, Georgia
RELOCATE IS AVAILABLE

Phone: +995 599 00 73 27 **Email**: set.adoyan@gmail.com

Telegram: defk1lla

Github: github.com/DefK1lla **LinkedIn**: linkedin.com/in/defk1lla

SUMMARY

Software development enthusiast with 3 years commercial experience on React, NextJS. I have experience in command and own projects developing (including pet and freelance), from simple landing pages to complex crypto marketplaces and online casinos. I am self-supporting, have good self education skills, and love to solve complex and interesting tasks.

EDUCATION

Georgian Technical University, Tbilisi

BACHELOR'S DEGREE SEPTEMBER 2018 – JUNE 2022

Faculty: Informatics and control systems

Speciality: Informatics

PROJECTS

- defk1lla.vercel.app
- github.com/DefK1lla/react-portfolio

WORK EXPERIENCE

Synmetrix

FRONTEND DEVELOPER AUGUST 2023 - PRENEST

Space Dog

LEAD FRONTEND DEVELOPER AUGUST 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Freelance

HTML CODER/FRONTEND DEVELOPER NOVEMBER 2020 - AUGUST 2022

SKILLS

- Frontend: TypeScript, JavaScript(ES5/ES6), ReactJS, Redux/Redux Toolkit, Mobx, Zustand, GraphQL, JQuery
- Backend: NodeJS, ExpressJS, MongoDB, Mongoose, HTTP, REST
- HTML/CSS: HTML, CSS, BEM, Bootstrap, Material UI, Styled Components
- Preprocessors: SASS/SCSS, LESS, Sylus
- HTML tamplate engines: Pug(Jade), EJS
- Instruments: npm, Gulp, Webpack, Git/Github
- Graphic editors: Figma, Photoshop, Zeplin
- Languages: Armenian (Native), Russian (Native), Georgian (Pre-intermediate), English (Beginner)

